Bryant Paz

Web developer

OBJETIVE

Full-stack developer with 2 years of experience designing and developing responsive, maintainable, and scalable web solutions. A big enthusiast of Linux, Neovim, Docker and open source. In search of an opportunity as a software developer.

MAIN SKILLS

Javascript Web Developer

React, Typescript, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Javascript, SQL, Lua, MongoDB, CSS, HTML, Git, Docker, AWS, Digital Ocean

EXPERIENCES

Javascript Full Stack

Coatí MX

July 2021 - February 2022 - 8 months, Mérida

Developing & managing "WellBe" - a digital & mobile platform linking company services with users for 24/7 reservation facilitation via a mobile app.

Javascript Full Stack

Yobain's Town Hall

January 2021 - June 2021 - 6 months, Merida

Service automation: sales, reservations, requests, and citizen support.

IOT Project Leader

Universidad Tecnológica Metropolitana

January 2020 - December 2020 - 1 year, Merida

Crash prevention system & customer support: speedometer, pedestrian alert LEDs, license plate grabber, fines generator.

Javascript Full Stack

UADY campus: Hunucma

January 2019 - December 2019 - 1 year, Hunucma

Developing & launching a teacher evaluation system on a website alongside inscription payments administrator.

EDUCATION

Information Technology Engineering

Universidad Tecnológica Metropolitana Mérida, México September 2019 - April 2021 - 2 years, Merida

T.S.U in Informatic Systems

Universidad Tecnológica Metropolitana Mérida, México September 2017 - August 2019 - 2 and a half years, Merida



CONTACT

plbryantt@outlook.com

www.bryantpaz.dev

9992431998

plbryant

in Bryant Paz

OTHER SKILLS

- Php/laravel
- Python/Tkinter/Django
- C#/ASP.net/MVC
- Nvim
- Linux
- SEO
- Tmux
- Figma
- Bash
- 100-130 wpm

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (native)
- English.B2 MCER

BIRTHDAY

• 28/06/1998

NATIONALITY

Mexican